[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Should they say with the man or should they always believe him if he, abuses them?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "they", "say", "with", "the", "man", "or", "should", "they", "always", "believe", "him", "if", "he", ",", "abuses", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Leave!", "answer_tokens": ["Leave", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Take me back, if you will, to the moment you came home and realized what was happening next door?", "question_tokens": ["Take", "me", "back", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "to", "the", "moment", "you", "came", "home", "and", "realized", "what", "was", "happening", "next", "door", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Thanks", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "I mean, that -- is that the reality of when you get caught in that kind of situation?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "--", "is", "that", "the", "reality", "of", "when", "you", "get", "caught", "in", "that", "kind", "of", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Did you know each other well?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "each", "other", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Yes, very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What was the first thing she said to you when you got to safety?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "first", "thing", "she", "said", "to", "you", "when", "you", "got", "to", "safety", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "You know, well, she -- first of all, I think we just wanted to breathe.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "well", ",", "she", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "we", "just", "wanted", "to", "breathe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What an incredibly -- is any there truth to rumors that you're thinking of wearing a cape now at work?", "question_tokens": ["What", "an", "incredibly", "--", "is", "any", "there", "truth", "to", "rumors", "that", "you", "'re", "thinking", "of", "wearing", "a", "cape", "now", "at", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "RB", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "EX", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "You know, I appreciate it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "appreciate", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What is your view, as a mayor of a big city in America, of the \"Stand Your Ground\" law?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", ",", "as", "a", "mayor", "of", "a", "big", "city", "in", "America", ",", "of", "the", "``", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "''", "law", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, I'm somebody that lives in the state of New Jersey where we don't have such a law.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "somebody", "that", "lives", "in", "the", "state", "of", "New", "Jersey", "where", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "such", "a", "law", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1976", "'76", "1971"], "LOCATION": ["Idaho"]}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "-NONE-", "CC", "-NONE-", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "When was that exactly?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "exactly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "It was 1976, '75 or '76, when I started to really seriously love to go to Idaho, and \"Tapestry\" was 1971.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "1976", ",", "'75", "or", "'76", ",", "when", "I", "started", "to", "really", "seriously", "love", "to", "go", "to", "Idaho", ",", "and", "``", "Tapestry", "''", "was", "1971", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What did you think of that moment then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "that", "moment", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I think it's just great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "just", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "When you sang that song like that, especially the way we just saw you singing there, when you look back at yourself there, knowing now what happened to your life then, what do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "sang", "that", "song", "like", "that", ",", "especially", "the", "way", "we", "just", "saw", "you", "singing", "there", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "at", "yourself", "there", ",", "knowing", "now", "what", "happened", "to", "your", "life", "then", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "I feel -- first of all, I am younger than all my daughters are now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "am", "younger", "than", "all", "my", "daughters", "are", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "You've been married four times now?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "married", "four", "times", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Third husband?", "question_tokens": ["Third", "husband", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Third husband.", "answer_tokens": ["Third", "husband", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 308, "question": "In your case, it'll be -- come on, how many dozen times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "case", ",", "it", "'ll", "be", "--", "come", "on", ",", "how", "many", "dozen", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "No, it would be --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "would", "be", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Did you marry every man you were properly in love with?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "marry", "every", "man", "you", "were", "properly", "in", "love", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "If I could have trapped you on a desert island with one man in your life that you had a relationship with, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "have", "trapped", "you", "on", "a", "desert", "island", "with", "one", "man", "in", "your", "life", "that", "you", "had", "a", "relationship", "with", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Again, hope springs eternal.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "hope", "springs", "eternal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What do you say to women who watch this or who read the book, who find themselves in that position, should they stay with the man or should they always leave him if he -- they -- if he abuses her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "women", "who", "watch", "this", "or", "who", "read", "the", "book", ",", "who", "find", "themselves", "in", "that", "position", ",", "should", "they", "stay", "with", "the", "man", "or", "should", "they", "always", "leave", "him", "if", "he", "--", "they", "--", "if", "he", "abuses", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Leave!", "answer_tokens": ["Leave", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "It's a reflective book of someone who's had a pretty amazing life in many ways, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "reflective", "book", "of", "someone", "who", "'s", "had", "a", "pretty", "amazing", "life", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Thank you for getting that about me, because I don't have bitterness.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "for", "getting", "that", "about", "me", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "bitterness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "And if I can't, why be bitter?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "I", "ca", "n't", ",", "why", "be", "bitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "What would be the moment -- if I had the power to let you relive a moment in your life -- it can't be marriage, certainly not marriage in your case -- we'd be here all night.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "moment", "--", "if", "I", "had", "the", "power", "to", "let", "you", "relive", "a", "moment", "in", "your", "life", "--", "it", "ca", "n't", "be", "marriage", ",", "certainly", "not", "marriage", "in", "your", "case", "--", "we", "'d", "be", "here", "all", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What's been the greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Piers, I've had so many great moments, honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "so", "many", "great", "moments", ",", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "And on Thanksgiving and Christmas and stuff like that, is there a moment when the piano gets wheeled out?", "question_tokens": ["And", "on", "Thanksgiving", "and", "Christmas", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "is", "there", "a", "moment", "when", "the", "piano", "gets", "wheeled", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Oh God, I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "God", ",", "I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I just keep all that separate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "keep", "all", "that", "separate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Isn't that an amazing power to have, that you can do that through the power of music?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "an", "amazing", "power", "to", "have", ",", "that", "you", "can", "do", "that", "through", "the", "power", "of", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Well, it's not my power.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "my", "power", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Tony Stern"]}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "What's the other song?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "other", "song", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "ING: The other one, which I wrote -- I co-wrote with Ms. Tony Stern.", "answer_tokens": ["ING", ":", "The", "other", "one", ",", "which", "I", "wrote", "--", "I", "co-wrote", "with", "Ms.", "Tony", "Stern", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "How does that sound?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "sound", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Sounds good.", "answer_tokens": ["Sounds", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Were you really trying?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "really", "trying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "You know what, I always like to make the guest feel like they're the star, you know, contrary to public perception.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "always", "like", "to", "make", "the", "guest", "feel", "like", "they", "'re", "the", "star", ",", "you", "know", ",", "contrary", "to", "public", "perception", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "So I think with you and Lionel, make you think you're better singers, it gives you more confidence?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "think", "with", "you", "and", "Lionel", ",", "make", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "better", "singers", ",", "it", "gives", "you", "more", "confidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "It's an ego booster.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "ego", "booster", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You've only sold what, 10 million albums?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "only", "sold", "what", ",", "10", "million", "albums", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "WP", ",", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Something like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Something", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Do you ever sing at home?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "sing", "at", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "But for fun?", "question_tokens": ["But", "for", "fun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Was there a moment?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I think there was a -- an instant the day I met him, 21 years ago, a connection there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "was", "a", "--", "an", "instant", "the", "day", "I", "met", "him", ",", "21", "years", "ago", ",", "a", "connection", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Because you were good friends for a long time?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "were", "good", "friends", "for", "a", "long", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "We were.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "But if you've had so many years as friends, what's the moment like when suddenly you both realize it's going to be something else?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "'ve", "had", "so", "many", "years", "as", "friends", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "moment", "like", "when", "suddenly", "you", "both", "realize", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "something", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I don't know how to describe it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "to", "describe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "He was must have been with you?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "must", "have", "been", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Of course, he was madly in love with me.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "he", "was", "madly", "in", "love", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "You know a lot about that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "a", "lot", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Is this even remotely healthy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "even", "remotely", "healthy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Is it just like a great, big, old fashioned southern pig out?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "just", "like", "a", "great", ",", "big", ",", "old", "fashioned", "southern", "pig", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I'm telling that you eat this and tomorrow you have a grape.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "telling", "that", "you", "eat", "this", "and", "tomorrow", "you", "have", "a", "grape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Which is your favorite of all this?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "your", "favorite", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I'm a salt girl, so I would go for the chicken.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "salt", "girl", ",", "so", "I", "would", "go", "for", "the", "chicken", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "What is this stuff?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "this", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "That's sweet tea.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "sweet", "tea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "And what are these little cup cakes?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "are", "these", "little", "cup", "cakes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "These are biscuits, basically.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "biscuits", ",", "basically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "So if I eat all of this, I would die, but with a smile on my face?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "I", "eat", "all", "of", "this", ",", "I", "would", "die", ",", "but", "with", "a", "smile", "on", "my", "face", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Did you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "I packaged the meat later.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "packaged", "the", "meat", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "How do you equate, though, this gorgeous food, which I would devoir in an instant, probably will the moment this interview is over, with the need in America, in particular, for people to probably eat less of this stuff?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "equate", ",", "though", ",", "this", "gorgeous", "food", ",", "which", "I", "would", "devoir", "in", "an", "instant", ",", "probably", "will", "the", "moment", "this", "interview", "is", "over", ",", "with", "the", "need", "in", "America", ",", "in", "particular", ",", "for", "people", "to", "probably", "eat", "less", "of", "this", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "EARWOOD: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["EARWOOD", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Even as you're eating that stuff, are you quietly thinking fried chicken?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "as", "you", "'re", "eating", "that", "stuff", ",", "are", "you", "quietly", "thinking", "fried", "chicken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Oh, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120413pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Daddy, is tonight movie night?", "question_tokens": ["Daddy", ",", "is", "tonight", "movie", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "It's why I keep doing it every single day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "why", "I", "keep", "doing", "it", "every", "single", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]